{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_6_04WFQP",
                "player_15_04WFQP",
                "player_11_04WFQP"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                6,
                15,
                11
            ],
            "animation": [
                "in_vehicle",
                "stand",
                "liedown"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A man with short black hair, wearing a white button-up shirt, dark pants, and black shoes. Light skin tone."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -8285.643,
                    2312.716,
                    211.267,
                    0.0,
                    -0.0,
                    -0.0
                ],
                [
                    -7724.577,
                    2066.467,
                    270.525,
                    0,
                    -9.009768679368023,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -7124.352,
                    1459.59,
                    214.105,
                    0,
                    -155.42941977588413,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "car": {
            "name": [
                "car_1_04WFQP"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                1
            ],
            "animation": [
                "None"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "White compact car with black grille, sleek design, and four doors"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -8325.24,
                    2114.316,
                    211.61,
                    0,
                    -12.559789289907357,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "BP_Hatchback_child_extras_C"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -7346.837,
            1562.585,
            199.154
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1323.3141496064218
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player",
        "car"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -6707.805,
            1417.579,
            237.578,
            0,
            151.7534132390999,
            0
        ],
        [
            -6736.876,
            2465.848,
            228.173,
            0,
            -154.7262145075638,
            0
        ],
        [
            -7006.511,
            1138.318,
            201.205,
            0,
            131.73743051184977,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, White_Compact_Car or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. White_Compact_Car",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. White_Compact_Car"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_white_shirt, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or White_Compact_Car?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. White_Compact_Car"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to White_Compact_Car, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many human figures are in a standing position in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many human figures are lying motionless in the snow?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many human figures are inside a car?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Among all the human figures, how many are men?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many human figures have a bald head?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many human figures have a medium skin tone?",
                "answer": "two"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. in a car",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "A. in a car"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. running",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. liedown",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "A. liedown"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in the brown sweater and black pants relative to the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in the black vest relative to the bald man in the brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in the white shirt relative to the bald man in the brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the front-left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in the white shirt relative to the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. In front of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in the brown sweater and black pants relative to the White Compact Car?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. In front of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the White Compact Car relative to the bald man in the brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Above",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Behind"
            }
        }
    }
}